Contact

swarrentexrn@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/shannonwarren-mba-msn-rn-agacnp-bcccrn-csc-cvrn-bc-tcrn-55812b49 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing

Lawson

Kronos

Certifications

CCRN

TCRN

CSC

CMC

TNCC

Honors-Awards

Sigma Theta Tau International Nursing Honor Society

Phi Theta Kappa National Junior College Honor Society

Dean's List ('95-'96)

Good Samaritan Scholarship for Nursing

National Society of Leadership and Success

Shannon Warren MBA, MSN, RN, AGACNP-BC, CCRN-CSC, CVRN-BC, TCRN

Trauma/Critical Care/Acute Care Surgery AGACNP-BC at Brooke Army Medical Center

Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Accomplished, highly motivated Trauma/ Critical Care/Acute Care Surgery AGACNP-BC with a diverse background in healthcare spanning over 22 years. I believe in being part of a collaborative team. I believe in the fostering of peer relationships and I am dedicated to building these positive relationships within and outside of my department.

Experience

Brooke Army Medical Center Trauma/Critical Care/Acute Care Surgery AGACNP-BC March 2020 - Present (3 months)

The University of Texas Medical Branch Nursing Clinical Instructor April 2019 - Present (1 year 2 months) UTMB School of Nursing

HealthTrust Workforce Solutions Critical Care RN Per Diem Float October 2019 - Present (8 months)

Houston, Texas Area

Memorial Hermann Health System

2 years 5 months

Trauma/ Critical Care Adult-Gerontology Acute Care Nurse Practitioner May 2018 - October 2019 (1 year 6 months)

The Woodlands

Critical Care RN Trauma/SICU

June 2017 - May 2018 (1 year)

The Woodlands

HealthTrust Workforce Solutions
Critical Care RN Per Diem Float
February 2015 - May 2018 (3 years 4 months)

B. E. Smith Interim Critical Care Nursing Leader 2015 - September 2017 (2 years) Texas

Carilion Clinic
Director CCU
June 2013 - 2015 (2 years)

Bayshore Medical Center Director ICU/ CVICU March 2012 - June 2013 (1 year 4 months) Pasadena, Texas

Contract Agency
Critical Care Per Diem Float RN
August 2011 - June 2012 (11 months)

Mainland Medical Center
Director Critical Care Services
July 2009 - August 2011 (2 years 2 months)
Texas City

Doctors Medical Center - San Pablo Critical Care Per Diem Float RN January 2006 - January 2009 (3 years 1 month) San Pablo

Agency-Contract
Critical Care Per Diem Float RN
December 1998 - November 2008 (10 years)
Houston-Galveston

California Pacific Medical Center

Critical Care Per Diem Float RN April 2006 - April 2007 (1 year 1 month)

St Lukes Episcopal Hospital CVRR Staff RN July 2005 - July 2006 (1 year 1 month)

Bayshore Medical Center Critical Care Staff RN October 2003 - June 2005 (1 year 9 months) Pasadena

UTMB

Critical Care Staff RN June 1996 - December 1998 (2 years 7 months) Galveston

Education

The University of Texas at Arlington

Doctorate of Nursing Practice, Nursing (2018 - 2020)

The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston (UTHealth)

Post-Masters certificate, ER/Trauma · (2017 - 2018)

The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston (UTHealth)

Master's Degree, AGACNP · (2016 - 2018)

University of Mary
MSN/MBA, Healthcare Administration · (2012 - 2014)

The University of Texas at Arlington BSN, Nursing · (2009 - 2011)